<resources>
    <string name="app_name">banksampah</string>

    <string name="desc_one">Here you can distinguish and sort each type of garbage properly. You can also easily sell your trash at the nearest trash bank. And get your coins!</string>
    <string name="desc_two">Make transactions with ease and redeem your coins with various attractive prizes</string>
    <string name="desc_three">Here you can find out how each separated waste can be recycled into useful and reusable items.</string>
    <string name="desc_four">You can visit the GreenT location or we will pick up your trash. So transact with your waste so that it doesnt pile up and can be reused.</string>

    <string name="type_one">"Container for organic food waste. Later this waste can be used as compost."</string>
    <string name="type_two">"With this trash can it can be easier to use it as a recycled craft or recycling in the factory."</string>
    <string name="type_three">"This type of waste must be separated because it usually comes from B3 (Bahan  Berbahaya Beracun)."</string>
    <string name="type_four">"This type of trash can is intended for residual waste. Non-recyclable waste. such as diapers, cigarette butts, styrofoam and used tissues"</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_news">Title News</string>
    <string name="detail_news">Detail News</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="news">News</string>

    <string name="information">Green Treasure is a digital waste bank that functions to increase awareness of the people of Padang City to dispose of waste in a disciplined manner and can help reduce waste in Padang City.</string>

    <string name="app">Green Treasure\nPadang City, 24255, Indonesia\n(021) 12131415-9\ngreent@gmail.com</string>

    <string name="info_pickup">Select the type and enter the estimated weight of the waste. There is no minimum weight limit for pickup</string>

    <string name="map_name">Location Green Treasure</string>
    <string name="api_map">AIzaSyD12u_UIAWYmimn6Qh7jheyDZu14OxZ2Xo</string>
</resources>